https://help.dyn.com/legal/privacy-center/

Oracle Privacy Center For Dyn ServicesEffective as of: April 1, 2017
Oracle recognizes that your privacy is important, and wants to make sure that you understand how your privacy is impacted when you use Oracle’s Dyn Services or visit one of Oracle’s Dyn Services websites.
As a leader in Internet Performance Management, there are a number of ways that Oracle learns information about the internet and its users.
To describe how Oracle collects, uses and shares information collected from you as clearly as possible, Oracle has created two distinct Privacy Policies, depending on which of Oracles Dyn Services or sites you are interacting with:
Oracle Privacy Policy For Dyn Services: This Privacy Policy describes how Oracle collects, uses and shares information collected from you through your use of Oracle’s websites for Dyn Services
(like www.dyn.com and other websites that reference this Privacy Policy) and the services offered through those sites.
Oracle’s Internet Performance Tools Privacy Policy: This Privacy Policy describes how Oracle collects, uses and shares information collected from you through your use of Oracle’s
Internet Performance Tools (like Oracle’s RUM Beacons, Recursive DNS services, and other websites or services that specifically reference this Internet Performance Tools Privacy Policy).
EU US PRIVACY SHIELD
Oracle complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework and adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to personal data that is received from the European Union. The Department of Commerce lists the participants in the Privacy Shield at https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions regarding Dyn’s privacy practices, please contact us:
By email:
privacy_ww@oracle.com
By mail:
Oracle America, Inc.
